Today is the forty-eightth.
Tamo together, right?
Stop looking at the camera Juninho do you want to set up an
Instagram for you or does he keep looking at the camera?
He raises his eyebrow like this o
stand there or your little hair all the time or here you have 1 white hair.
Take
will not have
for a change,
don't you?
This is Caio's life in the world.
worth it later.
I'll take it there tomorrow.
I travel to the lecture so I said bro let me organize the house.
He still has to stop by the barbershop to bring
a marketing plan to the guy I was redoing.
And then Jéssica has coffee?
More trick replacement
a brother my man here he is going to give me a ride here today and there
it's pasta mano because there it strengthens i'm without a car chevas
tá there mano arrived but tá without a piece i went with Juninho after
part again today and then you can put it here back
my man speaks late but that's enough,
right? Brother?
Guess it had to be a Chevette.
Chevette is only a problem.
And then girls bye girls all the best to you until the next one
girls.
Thank you from the heart.
Sorry for the delay.
Sorry for the pix instability.
Beijão tamo is back with God,
huh?
You called me so it was quick,
huh? Bro?
What a rush partner is gone now I came here at the barbershop
I've been doing that marketing action.
Dude I made some videos for them.
They'll see if they approve too.
I leave some truffles here too.
And then my dear,
I feel great about you.
Is Janeirão there?
Well my dear I think it was nice.
Within the culture narrative about behaviors where you want to go to understand
the leader's goals align with marketing to do 1 Brain job and position stop.
It's going well here,
man.
A marketing strategy.
It didn't just come through a video.
I was talking to him about it.
It's being nice because the guy is accepting my suggestions and he's on.
That's exciting bro.
You have to see the chevas.
How are you?
The boss took out the carburetor to clean it up.
There's a thing missing to call a rotor and there's a
lot missing here but at least it's here,
right bro?
Nine days without horses.